

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Caecus Design

Web & Graphic Designer / Owner Monmouth, OR Feb. 2016–Present

Subcontractor for companies in the Salem area, predominantly 5ive Marketing. Managed other subcontractors, assigning tasks and doing weekly meetings on current objectives. Focus on front-end web development, web advertisements, and print publications.

PAZ Design Group

Web Developer Salem, OR Jun. 2013–Feb. 2016

Assist the senior web developer in the production of websites, email advertising, making alterations and troubleshooting existing content, designing and building web page templates.

Worked extensively with Oral Biotech, CariFree, Remin Media, and KeySmile providing marketing strategies, pamphlets, front-end web development, and SEO strategies.

EDUCATION

Applied Baccalaureate

Western Oregon University, Monmouth OR Sept. 2016–June 2019

■ Major: Computer Science

Associates of Applied Science

Chemeketa Community College, Salem OR Sept. 2010-June 2013

- Visual Communication Interactive Media
- Visual Communication Graphic Design

SPECIALTIES

















SKILLS

Communication

- Maintain clear, consistent and timely communication with team members and clients to solve design problems and troubleshooting issues
- Participate in constructive critiques providing feedback that improve marketing effectiveness

Business

- Develop effective client management databases using Filemaker and Drupal for 30 years worth of client data
- Execute solid design that corroborates creative direction with the marketing team
- Advance the creative process with limited supervision while in a team environment
- Effectively manage multiple project deadlines

Design

- Experienced in the creation and development of Drupal websites
- Code cleanly and effectively in HTML & CSS
- Integrate existing JavaScript & PHP libraries
- Create documents with solid technical skills in Adobe Creative Suite



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Crash Security

Malware Analyst/Reverse Engineer/Tech Support Owner Corvallis, OR Jan. 2017-Present

Self-employed Malware Analyst and Reverse Engineer -Used IDA Pro and Hopper to reverse engineer malware. I primarily work within the macOS environment, but I have experience within the Windows OS as well.

Stahlbush Island Farms, Inc.

IT Administrator Corvallis, OR Jun. 2017-Sept. 2018

Worked with Active Directory to manage accounts. Assisted in coding programs for use on the farm. Worked with SQL servers as well as Microsoft Server. I also worked with different networking frameworks such as: TCP/IP, HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, RPC, DNS, DHCP.

Simply Mac

Service Manager / Master Technician Corvallis, OR May. 2015-May. 2017

Turned our store into a Premium Service Provider, driving both sales in retail and service. Co-Developed the "Security Bundle" which launched company-wide, in 73 stores, on September 1, 2016. As Master Technician, I held my ACMT and ACiT certification working on all iPhones and computers. Led our company in Gross Profit in my first month holding the Service Manager/ Master Technician position. Launched and led our locations iPhone repair launch prior to taking the manager position.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

Western Oregon University, Monmouth OR Sept. 2016-June 2019

■ Major: Computer Science

High School

Monroe High School, Monroe OR June 2008

SPECIALTIES

















SKILLS

Communication

- Comfortable at public speaking and able to maintain clear, consistent and timely communication with team members and clients to solve design problems and troubleshooting issues
- Participate in constructive critiques providing feedback that improve marketing effectiveness

Coding

 Code cleanly and effectively, frequently commenting code for understanding.



CAREER OBJECTIVE

A professional Software Engineer with accompanying degrees in Computer Science, Mathematics, and Economics committed to applying the most-up-to-date computer science and mathematics research to create trustworthy and reliable software for critical systems.

EDUCATION

Triple Bachelor of Science

Western Oregon University, Monmouth OR Chemeketa Community College, Salem OR Sept. 2008–June 2019

- Computer Science
- Mathematics
- Economics

EXTRACURRICULARS

Byte Club

- Project Manager
- General Officer

Cybersecurity Club

Project Manager

Math Club

President

Pi Mu Epsilon Chapter

President

Honor Society Memberships:

- Pi Mu Epsilon
- Phi Theta Kappa
- Phi Kappa Phi

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Persistent problem-solver with academic experience and skills concentrated toward use of logic, math, programming, science, and critical thinking as essential tools for addressing any given context.

Known for sustained hard-work, analytical mindset, agreeable bearing, and detail conscientiousness.

Committed to always learning more where time and opportunity permit and using what is known to best resolve the current problem at hand in ways that add value. Seeks an environment that offers unique challenges of a technical and theoretical nature.

SKILLS

- Programming, mathematical proof techniques, data analysis, clear writing ability, active listener, general problem-solving, resilience, coordinating groups and events in a timely manner
- Wrote a 44 page long capstone paper on elements of algebraic topology and a classification theorem for certain topological structures and hosted an educational learning seminar session on topology.

Computer Science

- Software Engineering
- Operating Systems
- Databases
- Data Science
- Microservices

Programming Languages

- Object Oriented, Declarative, Functional, & Imperative
- Java, C#, Python, SQL, Haskel, Matlab, C, Assembly

Web Development

- Front End, Back End, Architecture/Platform
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, C#, ASP. NET, MVC5



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Independent Contractor / Consultant

Salem, OR

May 2017-Present

- Contributed in the development of Android applications for clients:
 - Key UI components, layouts, and backend functions
- Followed detailed instructions provided by clients to ensure all tasks were completed to specification
- Completed tasks with limited / no supervision
- Effectively used resources provided by clients to complete tasks
- Utilized various software development tools to complete tasks, specifically Android Studio and Hyper-V

I.S.A Corp.

Production / Machine Operator Salem, OR May 2011-March 2013

Maintained and operated equipment at the production facility, processing raw materials for market preparation, and conducted regular quality control checks to ensure equipment functionality and product integrity

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

Western Oregon University, Monmouth OR Sept. 2017–June 2019

■ Major: Computer Science

Minor: Mathematics

Transfer Degree

Chemeketa Community College, Salem OR Sept. 2013-June 2017

■ Computer Science & Information Systems

SKILLS

Software Engineering

- Collaborated in a small team environment to create our own interpretation of an approximation algorithm for the Zero Sum Set NP Complete problem
- Planned, designed, and implemented a fully functional scientific calculator in Java using JavaFX
- Created five prototypes, and two completed games, using Game Maker Studio with GML (Game Maker Language)
- Knowledge of, and experience with, object oriented, declarative, functional, and imperative languages
- Consistently able to write clean, effective, and well-commented code
- Extensive experience in the planning and designing phases of project creation
- Experience designing, creating, and implementing databases of various sizes using SQL

Desktop Software

- Comfortable developing in QT Creator, NetBeans, Eclipse, Android Studio, and Visual Studio 2017
- Extensive experience using Microsoft Office, specifically Word, Excel, and PowerPoint

Operating Systems Setup and Management

- Installed multiple versions of Windows OSes across more than twenty workstations
- Installed multiple versions of Linux OSes across ten workstations and personal desktops
- Assisted individuals with computer configuration, setup, and maintenance
- Administrated a Linux file-and-web-server entirely through remote command line interface (SSH)